1215 E Lemon St., Apt 129, Tempe, AZ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Software developer focused on web and mobile development. Have a solid background in Javascript and J2EE. A quick learner and an excellent team player. Interested in a position of software development engineer. Previous working experience in various web application development and have an in-depth knowledge of:

- Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, AngularJS, NodeJS
- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap

• Java, SpringMVC, Hibernate

• Web RESTful Service, JSON, SQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer - DesignAShirt.com

May 2014 - Present (7 months)

- **Developed an AngularJS-based hybrid Android app**, Production V2, to monitor and update order status.
 - ✓ In the initial version, built the responsive front end, handled the sophisticated business logic.
 - ✓ Implemented real-time communication and barcode scanner. Built the Android app with PhoneGap.
 - ✓ In the optimized version, developed timeline module, search module, and automatic update module.
 - \checkmark Production V2 app has been delivered to Production Department to test.

(Working with AngularJS, Ionic Framework, PhoneGap, socket.io, Jenkins, Git, JSON).

- **Zendesk App**, for customer service team to check order and customer information.
 - ✓ Retrieve data from admin system via Cross-Origin Resource Sharing.

(Working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, HandlebarJS, Git, JSON).

- Developed an ASP.NET MVC based web application for outsourced printers to manage their allocated orders.
 - ✓ Developed a set of RESTful Web API to communicate order status with Admin system.
 - ✓ Implemented business logic. Handled data persistence. Set up email and error logging system.
 - ✓ Created dynamic front end, and used asynchronous update heavily. It has already been used in producation.

(Working with ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework, JQuery, AJAX, Elmah, Bootstrap, Git, SQL Server, JSON).

Developing new features for company public website and internal systems. Mainly working around front end.
(Working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Jenkins, Blitline API, Sauce Labs, Selenium, ASP.NET, Git, SQL Server).

Software Development Intern - Pearson

June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

- Developed a Python web application, Nibiru, which automates software installation in Amazon EC2 instances.
 - ✓ Developed a new service to automatically provision a cluster of EC2 instances with ElasticSearch installed.
 - ✓ Developed a module to dynamically handle allocation/association of Elastic IP and attachment/deletion of EBS volumes.
 - ✓ Developed a script to extract team name and create a tag with the team name for each instance.
 - ✓ Review pull requests of other team members. My code had already been integrated into the production environment. (Working with Python, Boto, Flask, WTForms, AWS, Jenkins, ElasticSearch, Git, Agile/Scrum, Linux).

Teaching Assistant - Arizona State University

Jan 2013 - May 2013 (5 months)

- Communicated to solve queries and helped students understand Object-Oriented Programming in Java.
- Helped students complete Java coding projects. Graded assignments, projects and exams.

OTHER PROJECTS

Secure Banking System

Sep 2013 - Nov 2013

• Developed a banking system with multiple security features. Working with Java Spring MVC, Hibernate, JSP, HTML, CSS, and MySQL.

Project Management System

Mar 2014 - Apr 2014

• Developed a web project management system which allows users to customize the components of their projects. Working with Java Spring MVC, Hibernate, JSP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, MySQL, JSON and Git.

Mobile Cloud Location-based File Sharing Service

Sep 2013 - Nov 2013

• Developed an Android file sharing system which supports file sharing between devices or via cloud. Working with Java Socket, Hibernate, MySQL and Amazon EC2.

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Science, Arizona State University, May 2014, GPA 3.55

Master of Science in Biology, Arizona State University, July 2012, GPA 3.96

Bachelor of Science in Veterinary Medicine, Nanjing Agricultural University, June 2010, GPA 3.93